[groaning]
[singing]
>> Excuse me.
Ladies
Ladies and
Get in.
Sorry, sir.
Sorry. Sorry, sir.
Sorry. Sorry, sir. Sorry. Sorry, sir.
Sorry. Sorry, sir. Sorry, sir.
Sorry. Sorry, sir.
>> Sorry. Sorry, sir.
It's a statement.
I'm big.
>> [laughter]
>> Nandini
New Year greetings, birthday greetings.
Manaslu
You there?
Rama Rajan Sri Rama Jayam.
Oh.
Uh.
So let them all talk.
>> [laughter]
>> Sorry.
At least we're jolly and got it here.
Mhm. Uh, any candy? Hey.
You pretty little doll. Mhm.
I better be back in a minute ready.
Hey, when you come in here doll. What
are you going to do with them cute
little thing in there, dear? Uh.
I see.
I probably had it here doll. Look at
what I mean. They're going to make it.
I do what you all want to do. Now I'm
back. What do we have for lunch?
I'm going to need you to go get them
all.
The weather.
I wish you had that candy that I had
earlier. What are you doing here? Hello,
what do you want to do? You better. I
don't care if you're going to get away
with all of that. I don't care if you're
going to get away with all of that. I
don't care if you're going to get away
with all of that.
Excuse me. You know what I had to do
today? What are you doing? I don't know
what we're going to put up with for the
next two months. I do believe we're
there. I don't know what we're going to
do. I can't get out of bed today. I
don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do.
Yes, sir.
No.
I don't know what to do. Mhm.
I don't know what to do today. Uh.
Hey, hey. I don't know what to do. I
don't know what to do today. What do you
want to do?
I don't know what to do first today.
Mhm.
I'm going to die. I got it.
I like it. I got it.
I got it.
I got it. I got it.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
I got it.
I got it. I got it.
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
>> [screaming]
>> I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
I GOT IT.
>> [laughter]
>> ANY PROBLEM?
DON'T TOUCH.
WE DON'T WANT THE FOOD.
SOMETHING.
Excuse me.
Just a minute.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
What is the problem?
Railway toilet.
I must write to the authorities.
Excuse me.
Mommy.
But number 72 can shift I go.
What you want, Mommy?
Mommy.
>> Wow!
I'm being
gas trouble
Hey! [groaning]
Mhm?
I walk into
You know you have a sudden problem. Fan
won't work. I don't know Rama.
Better look at the attic. So cool. You
can never look at the attic. You can
never look at the
Sir, in the train there
people are traveling.
You can never look at
You can never look at the
You can never look You can never look
You can never look
You can never look at the attic.
You
You know that.
Sorry, sir.
Another chance.
You are mega.
Cool effect.
You are not going to make it.
movie
Nandini
I'm making
You're making
I don't know.
I don't know. I'm making
I don't know, sorry.
I'm making you a love letter.
love letter I don't know what it is.
I don't know. I don't
I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
promise
love letter
May I come in? They will like
I don't know.
romantic I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. public service commission
I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know.
I don't know. I don't know.
Don't worry. I will never make a
mistake.
>> [music]
>> Love letter.
Love letter.
>> [music]
>> Love [singing] letter.
>> So sweet.
Love letter.
>> Beautiful family.
But
>> [clears throat]
[music]
>> Permission to relay.
I'm a very decent
Yes, sir.
>> [laughter]
>> Finger prints collected?
Photo?
RPF could have
>> [music]
>> Huh.
>> [sighs]
>> Khabib Kubam.
Sir.
Are they all the same?
Khabib Kubam.
Khabib
Kubam.
>> [music]
>> Shut up!
>> [screaming]
>> Sir.
My God.
I'm sorry, sir.